

Designer

Ambition

An enthusiastic and determined individual who has over 2 years' experience working in the digital industry. My goal is to join a digital agency where I am able to utilise my firm understanding of user-centered design, strategic problem solving abilities and inspire creative solutions in a collaborative environment. Passionate about creating products full of convienient user interactions and well structured content, whilst focusing on client's requirements and user needs. A keen learner who strives to continually build on valuable skills to achieve the most effective project outcomes. My ambition is to develop a career in the digital industry as a first class User Interface Designer.

Experience

John Lewis

User Interface Designer, December 2016 - Present

Working on the new plan-partnership Workforce Management system, by creating and iterating on low fidelity prototypes, visual designs and CSS styles for the multi-million pound system.

Freelancing

Web Designer, October 2015 - Present

Using problem solving abilities to design multiple web and print based solutions such as banners, logos, flyers and webpage layouts for multiple clients. Writing valid code under the W3C standards to develop websites mainly using Bootstrap. Communicating with clients on a regular basis to focus on project planning, discuss ideas as well as enhancements.

Reinvent Systems

Web Designer, June 2016 - October 2016

Worked remotely to design and develop responsive websites from scratch using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap as well as Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator. Used Umbraco CMS to input and manage content on client's websites. Used current knowledge of design trends to brand and create web-based graphics such as logos, infographics, icons and banners. Produced useful solutions for businesses under the health, education and finance industries. All work produced was committed through an agile workflow.

Webfold

Junior Designer, September 2014 - September 2015

Developed several user-friendly landing pages which lead to receiving more attention on client's business campaigns, whilst also creating diverse design solutions for web and print mediums. Contributed to modifying and maintaining various content on WordPress websites and HTML email templates. Actively participated in brainstorming and discussing design proposals, in addition to helping the entire team complete jobs on-time and effectively.

Education

E-learning

Front-end Development & Design Courses, October 2015 - Present

Spending time enhancing and learning new skills by committing to various tech courses online.

Digital Native UK

IT Apprentice, September 2014 - September 2015

Studied for an Advanced Level Apprenticeship in IT, Software, Web and Telecoms Professionals whilst working at Webfold.

Hamstead Hall Academy

A-level Graphic Design Student, September 2012 - June 2014

Course and exam work involved producing print and digital material to promote products and services. Achieved a grade A.

Details

gopskaur@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/gopskaur gopskaur.com

Expertise

Strong:

User Interface Design

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Balsamiq Mockups

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Knowledgeable:

User Experience Design

Sketch

Git

Conferences

Web Summit 2016

Interests

Data Visualisation Photography Dilruba Baking